There is a customer who had done online insurance.
Now his car met with an accident and
he got it done, then according to him, at the
time of settlement, it was found out that there was a voluntary duty of Rs. 14000 in his policy, but
if he makes a claim then he will have to pay
Rs. 2000 on the contrary, but the biggest thing is that
he did not know this,
he had to pay Rs. 2000 in the policy.
Hello friends, nowadays everything is
going online, so how can the insurance industry lag behind in this. There are
many plots for online policies,
such policy market has become available on Google, on the
phone, Paytm and every insurance company has its
own website through which you
can do online insurance policy.
Hello friends, definitely
if you do car insurance on online platform then the
premium is a little less and you
can do it sitting at home, which means it takes less time too
friends, but my experience says
that if you do online policy without thinking or knowing anything, then
later you get
stuck in the time of doing PM, then
friends, I will tell you  I will
tell you one thing, if you take care at the time of taking insurance, then there will never be any
problem,
and even if you are getting
insurance done offline through an agent,
it will still help you. I have
already taken Compliant
Services and Liability Insurance,
friends, whenever you are getting insurance done
online, see, the premium is
showing for liability insurance or
comprehensive insurance,
liability means third party insurance,
in this you do not have insurance for the vehicle,
if there is an accident, if
someone gets harmed by your car and
if he makes a claim on your car, then the
insurance company gives him
liability insurance and I have
set a reminder for the insurance, at the
press conference beans, friends, I will tell
you when there is damage to both the TP and the vehicle,
so friends, according to me, you have to take a
friendship policy, but if you
never drive the car, sometimes drive for a day
and keep a lot of vehicles in which there is
no chance of theft, then you can
take finger liability insurance,
whose premium is very low, but
my suggestion is  Now it is always with a low principal. The
second is DON'T cover. Friends, everyone knows that
whoever has a vehicle claim,
gets a much lower premium in insurance than the actual cost. To
reduce this reduction, you can take DON'T. The
premium of the garden is a little bit.
Now the more you add
to your policy, the more you benefit, but the
premium is a little higher. There are many DON'T additions.
If it is for consumer
goods and engine cover,
withdrawal, I have already made a detailed video on this.
You will find the link in the i button and
in the description. Now, definitely check
that at the time of insuring your vehicle, you must
take at least the minimum premium addition, which will be of
great benefit to you at the time of PM.
Third is ID. ID means ID and
declared mail. This is the complete ID of your vehicle
which the insurance covers.
Whenever your vehicle is totaled or stolen,
you get a clearance on it. The
lower the ID, the lower the premium.
Whenever you get insurance done online,
definitely check that you have got an option to
reduce the premium.  Are you not reducing your ID in this affair?
I always keep my ID as much as possible because
after that comes the Inchi factor. All these
mean no claim bonus that whenever you do
not take any claim of the vehicle within a year, then
when you get the insurance of the second vehicle done, then
you
get 20 percent anniversary which is an
addition, you get it on the premium
and this continues from 20
percent to 50 percent.
I have made a detailed video on this also,
I will put it in the link description, do
check it. So at the time of taking the policy,
definitely see the declaration of NCP
because if you give a wrong declaration,
if you have taken a plane and then take a lemon, then
your MB can become no claim, so do
check this. The
fifth and most important is Bollywood
Tools
1300. This is friends, there is a discount
which you get on the premium,
but in return of this, you get a huge
amount Tilak whenever you do it,
like I had
given an example in the first video that if your  The
premium is 10,000 and in that you
take a Discover of thousand in which the
company puts a deductible of 15000, so whenever you
do a small insurance of 12000 or 15000,
you do not get it because that much defect is
incurred earlier, if there is some big defect then
you get that amount after it is cleared, so
friends,
never take Bhole Bhandari Due from your police to reduce the premium, it
also takes time in getting the insurance done,
you must check it,
Hello friends, these are the five things which
if you keep in mind then you will never get stuck at the
time of getting the insurance done and
finally, whenever you get the police, do
check it whether there is some delay somewhere or
not and if you have taken these things mistakenly as I told you
or something wrong has happened then
immediately tell the companies and get it
changed, so
friends, if you liked this video then do
like it and do subscribe to this
channel for information on car insurance,
thank you.